I created a complete Amazon listing
image [music] set using nothing but
Google's new AI image generation model,
Nano Banana Pro. Now, I did this with a
purposely difficult product. I did it
with a product that has text on the
label. Some of the text is very small
and hard to read. And I did it with a
product where [music] it's difficult to
show what it visually does because it's
not something that actually works in the
real world. It's a skincare product. And
I did this purposely so that we could
put this to the test and see if Google's
Nano Banana Pro could really create a
full Amazon listing image set. And the
answer, spoiler alert, is yes. But, and
I'll [music] tell you what the butt
means in a little bit because throughout
this video, you are going to learn how
to create a complete listing image set
using Nano Banana Pro. But I'm also
going to show you what it can't do and
some of the drawbacks and things that it
really struggles with and what to do
about it. I'm also going to give you
access to a couple free resources that
will help you as you're going along
doing this [music] yourself. So, stick
around in the video and I'll give access
to that to you guys in a little bit. But
first, let's jump right into it. So, the
product that I chose, I actually have in
front of me right here. This is a
rosemary oil. The reason this is a tough
product is because it's a product that's
a bottle with a label that has text on
it, which is something that AI has
historically always been bad at. Nano
Banana Pro is the best AI image
generation model to handle that, but it
still has its issues. This is something
that it's just very difficult for AI to
master. And the other reason why this is
a difficult one is because it's hard to
visually show what it does. [music] I
have another YouTube video on Nanobanana
Pro where I showed using NanoBanana Pro
to create a listing for a diffuser,
which is something that actually does
something in the real world, like this
3D reality around us. It's you could
show it in an office spraying out the
diffuser oil. You could show it in a
home, in a living room, spraying out the
diffuser oil. But when it comes to a
beauty product like this, it's difficult
to show it in use because it's not
something that actually has action in
the real world. Like you can't show for
headphones, for example. I can show
somebody putting on headphones and
jamming out to it. Ow. I can show
someone putting on headphones and
jamming out to it. But a beauty product
like this, it's a little bit more
difficult to show it in action. So, my
goal by the end of this is to create a
full listing image set [music] with
every potential graphic. And what I'm
going to do is I'm actually going to
compare it to the actual listing for
this product that's currently live on
Amazon, which looks like this. So, here
is the actual live listing for this
product. This is actually a top selling
product in [music] this space. You can
see it's got over 100,000 reviews. And
to be honest, the listing images are
really not that good. They could be
better. So, we're going to try to beat
this for a top ranking product using
just Nano Banana Pro. So, I took these
four images and the prompt I used was
create a clean photo rendering of this
product to be used as the primary image
on an Amazon listing. This is a prompt
that I've had luck with in the past.
[music] Let's see how it does. Okay, so
first of all, so far it looks good. So
just looking at it, it seems to have got
the dimensions right. It looks clean. It
looks nice. It's true to form from the
actual bottle. Like the ratio of the
dropper to [music] the bottle itself is
right. It looks good. Now, let's take a
closer look at it. So I'm going to tap
the image in the chat and zoom in. And I
can see that it actually got the text
really close to dead on. [music] At
least it seems that way until I zoom
into this part, this little seal. And
there I see gibberish. [music] It says
100% in the middle, but on the top it
looks like it says Vegemite. That nasty
stuff that you Australians eat. And down
here, I can't even tell what that says
[music] at all. So, what you want to do
in this situation, every time I
encounter this, you think, "Ah, damn it.
It didn't work or it it messed up." Like
one little detail, you want to hit this
button in the lower right that says
save. Tap that and it will download the
full res to your to your phone or your
desktop depending on what device [music]
you're using it on. And once it does
that, it actually adds another layer of
processing. [music]
So it will actually look different the
item that you just downloaded than the
one that you're seeing in chat. [music]
So I'm going to try that. Download it.
Open it up in the gallery. And I'm going
to zoom in. And I can actually see that
it does in fact look different. Like
compare that to this the image that I
see in chat. There's definitely a lot
more detail there. The lines are
clearer, but the text is still
gibberish. That's the issue. So, what
we're going to do to try to fix that is
we're going to [music] go back into the
app. So, my next prompt, I'm giving it a
closeup of that part of the label. And I
say, "Try again." But the text on
[music] this part in the circle should
say premium quality guarantee. So, I
give it that context [music] and it
gives me another image very similar to
the other one. And it actually looks a
little better, but it actually got the
thing wrong. Like in the middle of this
circle, it's supposed to say 100%, not
the word quality. So, I know that's
going to be wrong. Even if I download it
and it's higher quality, and I say try
again, the seal is still wrong. It
should say 100% [music] in the middle,
premium around the top of the circle,
and quality guarantee around the bottom
of the circle. [music] refer to the
image attached and it gives me this was
like okay buddy you want to see that so
clearly we're just going to put it
outside the bottle and I was like uh
okay so I said the seal looks correct
because it did do it perfectly right
actually
place it on the bottle instead of next
to the bottle then it gives me this
again which is basically the same
gibberish that I had before I tried
downloading the image I open it up and I
see that it actually did on the
downloaded image get the word premium
even though it's not perfect [music]
and it almost got guarantee and it got
some of quality. So the downloaded image
still looks better but it's just [music]
not good enough. It's still you can just
tell that it's AI gibberish there or
it's just AI generated. It's not
gibberish but it's AI generated. So,
what I decide to do here is, [music] and
this is a common thread when you're
using Gemini, is sometimes you just need
to abandon chat. Okay, so at this point,
I'm pretty much ready to abandon chat.
But I try one more thing where I say,
"Close, but the words are still not
clear on the seal. Make sure the words
premium and guarantee can be read."
[music] and I get this, which again, you
can't tell in the chat, but if I
download the image and then I open it,
you can see it actually did better, but
now it it forgot the [music] word
quality. So, I see that I'm not getting
in this chat. And this is always when
you want [music] to start a new chat.
So, what I did this time, I started a
new chat where this time from the very
beginning, I included one image that had
[music] a closeup of this seal. So, I
started with a very similar prompt, but
this time I addressed the seal. So, I
said, "Create a clean photo rendering of
this product for the primary image of an
Amazon [music] listing. Note that the
text in the circular green seal says
premium 100% [music] quality guarantee."
And this is what it gave me. So, if I
zoom in here, it looks a little wonky,
right? But if I download the image, open
it up now, I can see it actually did get
it. Premium [music] 100% quality
guarantee. So now I've got a primary
image that I can actually use on an
Amazon listing and it looks nice. Now
here's where I'll say my first caveat. I
had to do a lot of back and forth to get
that seal to show properly. And in
reality, there actually still is a
slight difference because on [music] the
bottle that I have, the the rosemary
picture is overlapping on top of the
seal a little bit. Whereas in my image
in Gemini, the seal is over top of the
rosemary. Now, this is a small detail
that [music] literally no one is going
to recognize, like maybe one out of a
100,000.
But still, if you wanted [music] to be
actually exact, then that's something
that you would need to likely go into
Photoshop or Canva to make that change.
Just look at this side by side with the
rendering that I got from Gemini. It's a
beautiful rendering. And in fact, it's
actually a lot better and it's more
accurate than the current primary image
of the product. Okay, so I've got my
first image out of the set of seven that
I want to get to have a complete Amazon
listing image set for the product. Let's
move on to image number two. Now, for
this particular product, what I want to
do for the second image is hit the top
four use cases right away cuz this is a
product that doesn't have one clear use.
Some people use it for their hair.
That's actually what I use it for. Some
people use it for their skin. Some
people use it to diffuse for focus and
memory. And some people use it for
massage. So I want to make sure that
everybody who fits into any of those
categories knows instantly that this is
for them. So for my next image, I want
to show the four top use cases of the
product. So I stay in the same chat
where I just generated the goodlooking
primary image of the product and I say
good. Now create four lifestyle images
of the product to be used on an Amazon
listing highlighting the four primary
uses people buy it for. And what I got
back is this. Notice that I didn't even
give it the top four use cases. And it
got them all right, which is pretty
wild. This is like Amazon on easy mode.
You don't even have to give specific
instructions to the AI model all the
time because it actually has the
context. It has the knowledge of the
whole internet basically. So, it already
knew that these were the top four use
cases. And these are the top four use
cases. These are the four use cases that
I was going to feed the AI, but I wanted
to see what it would do on its own, and
it actually got them right without me
even telling it, which is pretty wild.
So, right away, I like this image. It is
clear to me looking at this image that
the bottle like almost looks like it's
kind of photoshopped in. But if you
don't do that and the bottle looks like
it's just sitting there, it looks very
dull. Like compare this with like this
sitting on my on my counter here. It's
like invisible basically. So you
actually do have to have it a little bit
artificially bright. The problem is here
if someone actually looked really close
at any of these images, they would see
that the text looks all freaky. Like if
you zoom in on this, you could see that
it doesn't say Rosemary. This is
Raffleberry.
And same on this image and this image
and [music] this image. Now, in reality,
is anyone going to do that? Nobody
downloads the Amazon images and actually
looks that closely at them. So, could
you get away with this? Yeah, it still
looks better than some of the factory
direct images you see on the listings
for factories that are selling their own
products, right? But if you don't want
people to know that you generated this
with AI, this would be a giveaway. If
somebody was looking for it, they would
be able to tell. So, what I'm going to
do instead is you have two options when
you run into this. There's no amount of
back and forth that's going to allow the
model to get [music] text this small
correct on an image. It's just not
possible. And what would you get if this
was actually an image? Even if you
photoshopped it, the text would still be
too small to read. It would just look
blurry instead of like AI gibberish. So,
you still wouldn't be able to zoom in on
and read that just because of the
definition, the resolution of the image
and how small the text is, but it would
just look like the right text, but
blurry rather than AI text gibberish.
And those are two very distinct things.
So, it's not that we need the text to be
readable. That's that's unreasonable and
you wouldn't get that without AI anyway.
But if you don't want it to be a dead AI
giveaway, then you do need to do one of
two things. One, you either take this
image that you got and Photoshop in the
rendering that you already had
generated. So, I would just hot swap
this out either in Canva or Photoshop
[music] with the the rendering that the
AI gave me. And that's a very easy job
to do. Photoshop has specific tools
dedicated just for this. So does Canva.
has something called the magic eraser.
You can just take out a object in an
image and then you can just replace it
with another object. So this is
something you can do with very little
training. With just like half an hour of
YouTube tutorials, you'd be able to get
it instantly. So that's option one.
Option two is work with the AI to
generate an image that wouldn't require
you to do any design. So, in order to be
able to do this exercise with you guys
and show you how to make a complete
Amazon listing at home with absolutely
no design whatsoever,
I'm going to use another prompt here
where I actually just re-uploaded this
image into the model and I just said
remove the bottle from these images and
just leave the dropper. And now I have
my four use cases without the tiny
bottle text. So that which would be the
dead giveaway of the AI, but it still
shows the use cases. Hair care,
skincare, aromatherapy, massage, and
bath. So I could still use this on my
listing and it's not required that the
bottle be shown in every image of the
listing. They already know what listing
they're on. So it's very clear that
we're talking about the benefits of this
product. They don't necessarily have to
be in every image. If it were me in my
portfolio, what we would do is the
Photoshop Canva [music]
design methodology to make it exactly
right the way we want. But that's
because we have in-house design
resources for you. You may opt to do
this where you just work with the AI to
do something that it can handle. Okay.
So, now we've got our first two images
for the listing. We've got our first
primary image with a white background.
That's a clean photo rendering of the
product. And we've got the top four use
cases of the product. The next image
that we're going to generate is called
the benefits graphic, and it's going to
show the top four benefits of the
product. This is a type of graphic that
pretty much every Amazon listing should
have. And by the way, if you don't know
what image options you have when you're
creating an Amazon listing, I have a
complete guide for secondary images of
an Amazon listing. It gives you 22
different options from benefits [music]
graphic, features, graphic,
instructional, competitor comparison. 22
different types of graphics that you can
include in your Amazon listing and you
could pick which ones fit your product
best that would best convert for your
particular product category and just use
those. If you want to get access to
that, you can download it in the link in
the description of this video. It'll be
the second link in the description of
this video and you can download it
there. But the benefits graphic is one
that pretty much any product can benefit
[music] from. It contributes to a high
converting listing in pretty much every
category. [music] So, in the same chat,
we use the following prompt. Now, create
a vibrant benefits graphic that
highlights the bottle in the middle of
the graphic with rosemary and essence
exploding out of the top of the bottle
with the top four benefits around the
bottle. The bottle should be realistic
like the first image you generated. The
final image should be mobile optimized
to be used on an Amazon listing. So, in
this case, you can see I was a lot more
descriptive, but I still didn't include
which benefits I wanted it to highlight.
So, I'm literally, again, I'm just
passing the ball to the AI and being
like, "All right, let's see what you
got, bro." And I have in my head, I
already know what the top four benefits
are of the product from my own product
research, but I'm literally just seeing
what the AI can do, seeing if it
generates the [music] four benefits that
I wanted to to generate. And here's what
I got. So, we're not off to too bad of a
start. Sometimes when you ask for a
benefits graphic, the AI is going to
give you something that's a little
cheesy or cartoony.
And this time we didn't get something
too bad. It is a little too busy.
There's too many colors going on. It's
not totally in line with the branding of
the product itself, which is literally
just white [music] and light lime green
in line with the the rosemary. So, I'm
not thrilled with it, but we're not off
to a bad start. I think I can work with
this. So, I'm not going to abandon chat.
I'm going to stay in the chat and go
back and forth in the chat until I get
something that I like. Now, let's talk
about what benefits it shows. I know
that the main benefits of this product
are skin health, hair growth and scalp
health, inflammation and tension, and
focus and memory. So, it almost got
those four. It was just a little bit
different. It said stimulates hair
growth, boosts focus and memory,
improves scalp health, and relieves
muscle pain. So the muscle pain one is
in line with the inflammation one and
the scalp health is also skin. Your
scalp is skin. [snorts] And literally
reading this I was like ah maybe the AI
actually knows better than me. So I
Googled it and the benefits that Google
had were very close to the ones that
Gemini generated which makes sense
because Google owns Gemini. So I
actually in reading this it was pretty
close. The only thing that I probably
would have swapped out is [music]
instead of relieves muscle tension, I
would have said reduces inflammation.
So, I decide to leave these four
benefits as the four main ones. But I
still don't like the design. So, I say
good, but make the text and icons
cleaner and more modern. There are too
many different colors. Ensure that the
final image is mobile optimized. And
then it gives me this. Now, this is
already a big improvement from this.
This looked a little too cartoony, a
little too many colors going on. And
this is a lot more simple. It's more in
line with the branding and the coloring
of the product itself. [music] So, we're
definitely on the right track, but I
still think it's too busy. So, again, I
prompt again where I say, "Try again
with a cleaner, more modern design." And
this is what I got. Now, this one I'm
actually happy with. I could go back and
forth to try some different designs and
get some more options. And that's
something that I probably would do, but
keep in mind that you don't have
infinite credits when you're working
with Gemini and you're working with Nano
Banana Pro. If you're on the free plan,
you're going to run out of credits
pretty quickly after just a small
handful of images. If you're on the pro
plan, you can definitely generate
probably a listing a day with this. And
if you're on the ultra plan, it's like
you'll never run out of credits. That's
for like professional designers. Now,
the pro plan is about 20 bucks a month.
The free plan is free, obviously. The
ultra plan is $125
per month as of the recording of this
video. It looks like the price may go up
at some point, but for most of you guys,
the pro plan is going to be all you
need. And that is 20 bucks a month. that
for normal Amazon sellers, brand owners,
if you're not doing design as your job,
then Pro is going to be plenty for you.
But I will say if you're on the free
plan, you're going to run out of credits
really quickly and it's going to take
you much longer to use this tool. So, if
you really want to practically use it on
your Amazon listings or your e-commerce
listings, the Pro plan is the right
plan. And they do have a free trial, by
the way. You can get Pro for free for, I
believe, 30 days until you get charged.
Okay, so now I've got my primary image.
I've got my use cases and I've got my
benefits graphic. The next image we're
going to generate is the features
graphic. So, I first I give it a try
with a very simple prompt and I say,
"Now create another graphic that has
[music] the top four features and this
is what I get." Now, I'm not happy with
this even though it's not too bad. The
good things are that it's mobile
optimized. It has Rosemary in it, but
it's just too kind of simple for me and
I [music] just didn't like the overall
vibe of it. You definitely could use
something like this, but I think it's
more appropriate to use something like
this in the brand story section as a
card [music] rather than one of the
primary images. So, we'll keep it in the
back pocket, but I try another prompt
that says, "Try again, but I want the
bottle in the actual image." And the top
four features should be that the amber
glass prevents oxidation and that it's
hand blended and that it's 100% pure and
that it is bottled [music] in the USA.
Because I didn't like the top four
features that it came out with this
time. They just weren't accurate. It
said 100% pure natural, steamed
distilled. That one's fine. Premium
quality, which doesn't really mean
anything, and cruelty-free, which that
actually [music] doesn't say that. So, I
don't want to make a claim that I don't
know is true. And also, I don't think
that's one of the top four features
[music] that customers actually care
about for this product. So, I gave it
some more data here, and it came out
with [music] this. Now, this graphic, I
think, looks bad to me. It looks like an
unskilled Fiverr designer made it and
[music] it doesn't look like something
that I would post. So, I just try to get
it to start all over. And I say in the
same chat, try again with a completely
new design concept to make it clean,
modern, and mobile optimized. I find
using the words clean, [music] modern,
aesthetic, they usually end up providing
good results when it comes to creating
[music] e-commerce listing images. So, I
use those words a lot. And when it
starts going off the rails or getting
too cartoony or cheesy, I [music] bring
it back in with those words, clean,
modern, and aesthetic. And they they
tend to produce good results. [music]
And so what it produced was this. And
this is something that I'm happy with.
It is mobile optimized. It's a good
design. It's in line with the design of
the product and the brand itself. It
shows the bottle and [music] it has the
four features that I talked about
perfectly represented here in a mobile
optimized way. I also like the little
icons that it chose. It chose this
little shield for amber glass
prevention. It showed the hand blended.
It's like two hands in a bowl. So,
[music] it looks good and I'm happy with
this. So, this is one I would post. It's
also in line with the design aesthetic
of the previous image. So, everything
[music] looks pretty cohesive and it
looks like, you know, one cohesive
[music] design between all the images.
So, now we've got four out of our seven
images already. our primary image, our
benefits graphic, our features graphic,
and our four use cases. Let's move on to
the last three. Okay, so this next image
that we're going to create is a
stepbystep instructional. So, even
products that you don't think have
instructions or they're very clear, the
step-by-step instructional can be a very
powerful graphic for driving conversions
because it does something called future
pacing, which means that the prospective
customer that's looking at the listing,
they can sort of vicariously live
through you as you show them the things
that they're going to do once they get
the product. So, because I know one of
the top use cases for this product is
dropping drops of it into a diffuser,
I'm going to put a step by step for how
to use this rosemary oil with a diffuser
in your home. So, what I did was I
started a new chat and [music] I
uploaded the original images that I used
to generate the primary image and I
said, "Create a beautiful, clean,
lifestyle image of this product to be
used on an Amazon listing." The image
should show a woman dropping a few drops
into her home diffuser in her cozy home.
The image should say, "Step one, add a
few drops. Step two, turn on diffuser.
Step three, enjoy better focus and mood.
Make sure the image is clean, simple,
and mobile optimized. And make sure to
follow the original branding [music] and
font." So, in this case, I actually did
give quite a lot of context because I
knew the steps that I wanted to be
included. I knew the vibe and design of
the image, and I didn't want to leave
much up to chance for the AI model. So,
this is something that you guys can play
with. Sometimes you can just leave it up
to the model and give it sort of a
general prompt with what you want and
see [music] what you get. And sometimes
when you know really exactly what you
need, you can provide a lot more context
and you have a better likelihood [music]
of getting the outcome that you're
trying to go for. And so what I got was
this image. And already I loved how this
came out. I thought this came out great.
It says step the step one, step two,
step three. The font is in line with the
font that's actually on the bottle. Uh
it's a very clean like an aesthetic and
bright image. It evokes the kind of
emotion that we would want with this.
The only thing that could be an issue
with this image is again the text on the
bottle. So if I zoom in on this image in
chat, you can see you really can't read
that text. It does sort of say rosemary
and the top you really can't read at
all. Now again, would you be able to
read this text if it was an image?
Probably not. The text, especially the
small text, would be blurry, but this
isn't blurry. This is AI gibberish. And
there's a difference between the two.
So, even though shoppers are likely not
going to zoom in that close on an image
like this, because the point of the
image, the bottle is so small that no
one thinks they're going to read the
text on that bottle anyway. It still
bothers me. I don't want people to know
that I used AI on my Amazon listings.
So, what I'm going to do in this
situation is swap that bottle out again
for the original primary image rendering
that the model gave me using the eraser
tool in Canva or using Photoshop. Now,
if you don't want to use any kind of
design whatsoever, even some kind of
free tool like Canva, you want to do it
all in AI and you had a tuck product
like this that had text on the bottle,
you could still do it without any design
just by asking the model to remove the
bottle from this image and keep the
steps and keep everything else about the
image, but just the bottle won't be in
it. And then you can still the image
still has the same impact. It's just
that you're not seeing the product in
the image, which personally I prefer. I
think it makes a better connection to
the customer. But if you wanted to, you
could do it. And still doing that would
leave you with a much better listing
than what's currently up publicly on
Amazon for this product. So, here's what
it looks like if I remove the bottle
from the image so that it can be
uploaded without any Photoshop
whatsoever. The only thing that I didn't
like about this is that there's one icon
per step except for step three, which
has two icons, which I think just
aesthetically doesn't look good. So, I
just said one logo per step. Literally a
four-word prompt. And it gave me this
final [music] image. So, this is what I
would upload if I wasn't going to use
any design tools whatsoever. But if it
was me and my team, I would stick with
this image and just use Canva Photoshop
to swap out the bottle for the right
bottle without any jibberion. Okay, so
on to the sixth image, which [music] for
this one, I wanted to highlight a
particular use case that just like the
diffuser one is one of the top use cases
for the product. So I can [music]
connect directly with that avatar, which
is women using it in their hair for
scalp health and for hair growth. So I
actually went back to the same chat that
I was creating the benefits and features
graphics in, and I said, create a
lifestyle image to be used on the Amazon
listing that shows a woman using it in
her hair. and it gave me this graphic.
[music]
So again, this has the bottle in it and
you know when I zoom in on this that
it's going to be AI gibberish and even
when I download the image [music]
that'll that'll make it better, but it's
still not going to be good enough to not
be AI gibberish. Now it says Rosemary on
it even when I zoom in this much and you
can see rosemary. So, in reality,
this honestly is acceptable because if
this wasn't AI, it would still be too
small to be readable. And see what the
full res image shows. And actually, it's
a lot better. If you look at the full
res image, compare that with the image
in chat. Here's what the bottle looked
like in chat. Here's what it looks like
when I download it from the chat. Big
difference, right? The actual logo of
the brand itself is now readable and
rosemary is much more clear and
essential oil underneath that is clear.
So actually it's really it's really not
bad. You have to zoom in really far to
see the text [music] that comes out AI
gibberish. And if this was a photo,
there's no way you'd be able to read
that tiny text anyway. The thing is it
would look blurry but not like
gibberish. There's a very distinct look
to AI gibberish text that looks very
distinct from just blurry text from it
being too small for a photo to render.
So if you wanted to make absolutely sure
that not a single person could prove you
used AI for this, then you still would
want to hot swap out the bottle in
either Photoshop or Canva. But we're
getting to the point where you're really
splitting hairs there because it
actually actually did a surprisingly
good job with the text on this small
bottle in [music] this image. So again,
if it were me and my team, I'm just very
sensitive about this in my portfolio. I
would swap it out and also there's no
reason for me [music] not to because we
have design resources inside my team.
But I I honestly wouldn't blame someone
for using this image straight up right
in their listing. However, since I'm
making this whole tutorial just to show
you guys how to make a complete Amazon
listing image set without [music]
any design whatsoever, just using Gemini
and Nano Banana Pro, I am going to
remove the bottle from this listing in
case any of you are like me where you're
very sensitive to AI gibberish. You
don't want anyone to know, but you still
want to use Google Nano Banana Pro to
create your Amazon listing. I use this
prompt. Looks good, but don't have the
bottle in the image. instead just show
just say in the image. I said show say
in the image that improves scalp health.
So it [music] put improve scalp health
there which I like the clean and like
simplicity of it but it just looks a
little awkward having the text there. So
I said move the text that says improve
scalp health to the upper right and add
the logo to the upper left. And I came
out with this image. Now this is a good
image. This image you could use on the
Amazon listing. And again, remember what
the Amazon listing looked like before
us. This is the public listing that's
currently on there versus here's the
images that we have so far. I would say
we're already doing quite a lot better
than what the listing currently has.
Okay. And for my final image, I took a
little inspiration from [music] the
guide that I mentioned you before, which
is the guide to Amazon listing secondary
image sets [music] that shows you all
the different options you have for
guides. Again, if you want to download
that guide, you can click the link in
the description of this video. And I
decided that a very important part of
[music] this product which
differentiates it from all the other
products on the market is that the size
is huge. Usually when you buy essential
oils, they come in these little tiny
bottles, [music] these little tiny
dropper bottles, but this is a massive
bottle of rosemary oil. It's 4 oz.
[music] And most of the other
competitors don't sell that much. So I
wanted an image that just highlights
just that. So, in the same chat, I use
the prompt. Now, create a comparison
[music] image to be used on the Amazon
listing showing the bottle in a woman's
hand and highlighting that there are 4
ounces in this bottle and show a
different competitor [music] with only 1
oz. And it gave me this image. Now, this
is not a bad image because it shows it
in someone's hand. It shows that it's
really big and it shows it compared to a
generic brand. And it did a good job. I
honestly think it's a good image. It's
just I don't like the woman in the
background. [music] I think it's
unnecessary. I always opt for cleaner,
more straightforward [music] and simple
designs that just they just communicate
a point without any [music] excess
noise. So, I said good, but make the
image simpler. Remove the woman from the
background. And I got this. Now, this is
a great image. It's mobile optimized. It
shows a very clear comparison visually
[music] and via text. And I think this
is completely ready for uploading.
[music] The only thing that we always
want to check again is the text here.
And I'll say it got the text really good
except for that little seal. So, we went
through that. We're going through the
same thing now that we went through
before with this little seal. And if I
download it and then zoom in, you can
see all the text is great. It's just
that seal is still gibberish. So again,
what I would personally do in this
situation is I would simply swap it out
for the other nanobanana image that we
generated for our primary image. But
what you can do if you don't again want
to use any Canva or Photoshop at all is
simply remove the seal and just say take
the seal off of the packaging and
[music] then it won't be there at all.
And if you again look at the current
listing that's up on Amazon.com, it's it
looks totally different than the
packaging. So, a small change on the
packaging is is not going to ding you.
Amazon's not going to not going to ding
you for that. You're not trying to like
deceive [music] the customers in any way
just by removing that. So, that would be
your option if you really didn't want to
use any design resources [music]
whatsoever for this particular product.
And here's the image that you would
generate. Now [music] again, there's no
way that anybody is going to notice that
that little green circle is missing from
the packaging. This is no [music]
problem to upload. And even though the
packaging is not exact, it's almost
exact. And if you really didn't want to
do any design whatsoever, you could
completely upload this and you'd be
totally fine. Now, I go a lot deeper in
the guide to using Nano Banana Pro for
Amazon sellers. It's an ultimate guide.
You can download it for free in the
description of this video. just click
the first link in the description of
this video and you can [music] download
the guide for free. I walk through a
totally different example there and
again create an entire Amazon listing uh
through that guide. So that's a good
thing to ride along with when you're
doing this by yourself at home. Just
download the guide and as you're
creating your listing, you can go step
by step through the different listing
images. And again, if you want to
download the SOP on how to create Amazon
listings in general with 22 options for
different listing image types that you
can upload to your listing, that's the
second link in the description of this
video. You can download it there. And
now we have created a complete Amazon
listing for this product with all seven
images ready to upload. Now, the next
step would be to generate your video and
that will be coming up in an upcoming
video on this channel. So stay tuned
there. But we are living in an
absolutely crazy time. This tool is one
of the biggest leaps that I've seen in
the last 10 years of selling on Amazon
that completely leveled the playing
field. There are huge players using the
tool. There are upcomers using the tool.
It just made everyone have access to the
highest quality listing images ever. As
you saw through this little exercise
that we did today, it does have its
drawbacks and it's not perfect and there
are some things that it can't get right.
And that's why I purpose purposely chose
a product that's a tough one because it
has a lot of text on a label and some of
it really small text on a label. That's
a really tough thing to produce with
Nano Banana Pro, but we did it in this
exercise. So, if you really wanted to do
it right and you really cared about
making the images perfect, then what you
would do is just take the images that
you got that did have the bottle in it
small that had some gibberish and you
just hot swap it out in Canva or
Photoshop. You don't have to be a
designer to know how to do that. You use
tools like the magic erase tool and then
hot swap it out. It's it's actually not
that difficult. But if you did just want
to use Nanabanana Pro, we showed you how
to use or I showed you how to use
Nanabanana Pro to generate a whole
listing image set without any design
whatsoever, even for a tough product
like this. So, take a look at the
original listing that we're dealing with
with the public listing currently on
Amazon, and take a look at the listing
we just generated, and you can use your
own judgment which one you think is
better. And if you want to see another
walkthrough of creating a full Amazon
listing image set for a completely
different product, I go through the
entire process here, plus a lot more
tips and tricks for how to use Nana
Banana Pro to [music] create an Amazon
listing. I'll see you guys over there.
[music]